Guide to the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society Records, 1961-2009 AIS.1998.51
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society Records
1961-2019
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society
AIS.1998.51
8 Linear Feet (6 boxes)
The Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society was formed in 1961. The mission of the Society is to bring to Pittsburgh notable performers and composers of chamber music as well as expose audiences to emerging chamber music groups. The papers of the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society include brochures, scrapbooks, programs, reviews, tax forms, posters, and WQED-FM radio station material concerning the taping of concerts.
History
In response to the loss of regular chamber music concerts once sponsored by The New Friends of Music (1938-1960), the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society was founded under the leadership of Harry Corbett in 1961. A number of distinguished academic, artistic, social, and business leaders of Pittsburgh formed the Society's organizing committee. Among these initial organizers were Mrs. Paul G. Benedum; Henry J. Heinz; William Steinberg, conductor of The Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra; Reverend John J. Wright, Bishop of Pittsburgh; and Edward H. Litchfield, President of University of Pittsburgh.
The mission of the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society is to bring to Pittsburgh notable performers and composers of chamber music as well as expose audiences to emerging chamber music groups. Many of these new groups featured by the society are winners of the Walter W. Naumburg Chamber Music Award.
The music of the old masters such as Beethoven, Haydn, Mozart, Schubert, Mendelsohn, Brahms, Dvorak, Ravel, Bartok and Hindemith is featured prominently at the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society's concerts. Together with this traditional chamber music fare, twentieth century works are also scheduled for most concerts. The society has commissioned some of the works presented in concert, which include David Stack's "Quartet 'Speaking Extravagantly' (1981)," Lou Coyner's "Eolith No. 4 (1984)," and "The Rewaking (1991)," a piece written by Pulitzer Prize winner John Harbison. The Chamber Music Society is also committed to promoting Pittsburgh artists such as Harry Franklin, piano; Bernard Goldberg, flute; Theo Salzman, cello; and composers Leonardo Balada, Lou Coyner, Stephen Foster, Nikolai Lopatnikoff, John Peel, David Stock, and John Harbison.
The Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society has earned a reputation as one of the largest, oldest, and most popular chamber music organizations in the country. Concert Seasons usually consist of five to six concerts. In the first three decades of existence, the society has presented over 100 concerts, with nearly 80 ensembles performing 549 works by 140 composers. Starting in 1976 much of this music has been taped and broadcast to an estimated 100,000 people through WQED-FM.
The Chamber Music Society has kept prices of concert tickets low in order to attract a diverse audience of students and community members. For operating costs and maintenance of the society the Chamber Music Society has traditionally depended on outside sponsorship. The Chamber Society's fledgling years were supported with money from the Howard Heinz endowment. This endowment sporadically supported the society throughout its history. Other sponsors have included Carlow College, Chatham College, the Community College of Allegheny County, Point Park College, University of Pittsburgh, The Pittsburgh Federation, and the Pennsylvania Council of the Arts. Since 1969, the chamber music has also regularly received grant money from the National Endowment for the Arts.
Scope and Content Notes
The records of the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society contain brochures, performance programs and reviews, tax forms, grant applications and papers relating to WQED-FM taping and broadcasting of the Society's concerts. Administrative business is documented in the Chamber Music Society's Minutes. Financial statements and tax forms provide financial information about the Society. Correspondence relating to individual and corporate sponsorship as well as papers and applications regarding grants provide further financial information and details about how the Society gains funding. Programs, pamphlets and posters from each season provide the names of artists, composers and the works performed at each concert. Additionally, there are reviews, press releases and publicity regarding the concerts. A history of the Chamber Society, its supporters, and a summary of the first thirty years of performances are found in the Anniversary Book (1991). Materials in this collection includes; minutes, brochures, programs, posters, tax forms, grant proposals, foundation information, scrapbooks and are arranged alphabetically within each fiscal year.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in chronological order by year. The years have been defined and divided by each fiscal year, dating from July of one year to June of the following.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These materials came to the archives as a gift from the Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society in December 1998 and June 2009.
Previous Citation
Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society Records, 1961-2009, AIS.1998.51, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh.
Chamber music -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- Societies, etc.; Societies; Music; Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society; WQED-FM 89.3 (Radio station: Pittsburgh, Pa.)
- Organizational Material, I.
  - Board Members, 1961-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws, 1963-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Concerts, 1961-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1965-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Naumburg Foundation, 1976-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - New Friends of Music (works performed), 1938-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fiscal Year Files, 1960-2009; II.
  - July 1960-June 1961
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - July 1961-June 1962
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - July 1962-June 1963
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - July 1963-June 1964
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - July 1964-June 1965
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - July 1965-June 1966
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - July 1966-June 1967
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - July 1967-June 1968
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - July 1968-June 1969
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - July 1969-June 1970
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - July 1970-June 1971
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Carnegie Magazine, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - July 1971-June 1972
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - July 1972-June 1973
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - July 1973-June 1974
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Minutes (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - July 1974-June 1975
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Minutes (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - July 1975-June 1976
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Minutes (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - July 1976-June 1977
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Earned Income Tax (Refunds) (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Minutes (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - WQED-FM (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - July 1977-June 1978
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Brochures (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Howard Heniz Endowment (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Minutes (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Taxes (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - WQED-FM (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - July 1978-June 1979
    - A.W. Mellon Educational and Charitable Trust (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, State of Arts Hearings (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Taxes (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - WQED-FM (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - July 1979-June 1980
    - A.W. Mellon Educational and Charitable Trust (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts, State of the Arts Hearings (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Taxes (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - WQED-FM (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - July 1980-June 1981
    - Anniversary Program, Plans and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Benedum Foundation (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Letters to Legislators (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Summerfest (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Taxes (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - WQED-FM (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - July 1981-June 1982
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Anniversary Program (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Anniversary Program, Plans and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Carnegie Magazine, Septmeber 1981 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Letters to Ruth Montgomery (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation, 82nd Annual Report (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Summerfest (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Taxes (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - WQED-FM (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - July 1982-June 1983
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Disbursement Requests, University Account (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Jackson, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Letters to Legislators (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Meet the Composer, John Peel (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Summerfest (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Taxes (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Vira I. Heinz Fund, Coyner Commission (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - WQED-FM (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - July 1983-June 1984
    - Administrative Papers and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Jackson, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Mid-Atlantic States Arts Consortium, De Capo Chamber Players (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Summerfest (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Taxes (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Vira I. Heinz Fund, Coyner Commission (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - WQED-FM (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - July 1984-June 1985
    - Administrative Papers and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Chamber Music America (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Jackson, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Mid-Atlantic States Arts Consortium, De Capo Chamber Players (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 20th Anniversary (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Publicity (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Taxes (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Vira I. Heinz Fund, Coyner Commission (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - July 1985-June 1986
    - Administrative Papers and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Brochures (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Chamber Music America (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Jackson, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Meet the Composer, John Peel (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Mid-Atlantic States Arts Consortium, De Capo Chamber Players (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - National Endowment for the Art, 20th Anniversary and American Music Week (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - July 1985-June 1986
    - Pennsylvania Council on Charitable Organizations (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Sales Tax Exemptions (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Publicity (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Taxes (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - WQED-FM (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - July 1986-June 1987
    - Administrative Papers and Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Brochures (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Chamber Music America (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Contracts (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Minutes (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Council on Charitable Organizations (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Foundation (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Publicity (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Taxes (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - VITA Award (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - WQED-FM (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - July 1987-June 1988
    - Administrative Papers and Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - American Music Week (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Brochures (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Contracts (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Harbison, John, Commissioned Music (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Long Range Planning Report (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Minutes (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania Council on Charitable Organizations (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Publicity (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Siberman Challenge (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Taxes (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Telemarketing (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - VITA Award (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - WDUQ-FM (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - WQED-FM (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - July 1988-June 1989
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - American Music Week (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Brochures, Including Photos (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Computers (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Harbison, John, Commissioned Music (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Minutes (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Orion Quartet (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Paid Staff (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Pennsylvania Council on Charitable Organizations (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society Board Survey (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Publicity (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Siberman Challenge (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Taxes (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - WQED-FM (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - July 1989-June 1990
    - Administrative Records and Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Fund Raising (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Harbison, John, Commissioned Music (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Leich, Roland (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Minutes (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Paid Staff (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Council on Charitable Organizations (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Publicity (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Shared Music Administrator Program (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Steinfirst Memorial Gift (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Taxes (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - WQED-FM (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - July 1990-June 1991
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Chamber Music America (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Harbison, John, Commissioned Music (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Mellon Bank Audience Development Fund (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Minutes (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Corporation Bureau (Name Registration) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania Council on Charitable Organizations (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Publicity (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Sponsorship (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Surveys, Audience (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Taxes (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - WQED-FM (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - July 1991-June 1992
    - Administrative Records (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Anniversary Program Book Plans (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Harbison, John, Commissioned Music (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Marketing Consultants (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Mellon Bank Audience Development Fund (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Pennsylvania Corporation Bureau (Name Registration) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Pennsylvania Council on the Arts (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Press Reviews and Publicity (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Tax (Amusement) (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - July 1992-June 1993
    - Administrative Records (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Anniversary Program Book Plans (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Mellon Bank Audience Development Fund (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Press Reviews and Publicity (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Tax (Amusement) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - July 1993-June 1994
    - Administrative Records (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Mellon Bank Audience Development Fund (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Press Reviews and Publicity (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Tax (Amusement) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - July 1994-June 1995
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - July 1995-June 1996
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - July 1996-June 1997
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - July 1997-June 1998
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Pennsylvania Sales Tax Exemptions (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - July 1998-June 1999
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - July 1999-June 2000
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - July 2000-June 2001
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - July 2001-June 2002
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - July 2002-June 2003
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - July 2003-June 2004
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - July 2004-June 2005
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - July 2005-June 2006
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - July 2006-June 2007
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - July 2007-June 2008
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - July 2008-June 2009
    - Brochures (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Programs and Reviews (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Scrapbooks, IV.
    - Scrapbook, 1961-1965 (Box 6, Volume 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Volume 2)
- Oversized Material, III.
  - Promotinal Flyers (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Promotional Posters (Box 5, Item 2)
- Commission Music, 2001-2009; V.
  - Allegheny Quartet by Albert Glinsky, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Beyond Words by Stephen Hartke (September 11th tragedy), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Clarinet Effect, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Crossings by Amy Williams, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Formations by Mick Haggerty, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Steel, Slag, and Silicon by Mark S. Fromm, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Posters, 1996-2019; VI.
  - Posters, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Posters, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Posters, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Posters, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Posters, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Posters, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Posters, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Posters, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Posters, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Posters, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Posters, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Posters, 2014-2016 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Posters, 2016-2017 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Posters, 2017-2018 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Posters, 2018-2019 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Various Posters, 1999-2003 (Map-case 1, Folder 1)
- Concert Programs, 1974-2016; VII.
  - Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Programs, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Programs, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)